

Enrique Zetina

Systems Engineer

+52 1 55 22 86 69 19



www.ezetina.com



linkedin.com/in/ezetina



github.com/ezetina86



jenzetin@gmail.com

About me —

I'm a Big Data Engineer with experience working with public cloud platforms and developing software using Java and Python. Certified as Google Cloud Architect, Google Cloud Data Engineer, Oracle DBA 11gR2. I'm curious and goal-oriented, very good learning and teaching new technologies and collaborating with team members.

Google Cloud Platform90%

PL SQL 80%

Big Data 70%

Python 60%

[Goal oriented, excellent technical skill, ability to solve problem quickly, team spirit]

Languages —

English 80%

Spanish Native

Education

2006-2013 Bachelor of Computer Science

Antivirtus and Antispam system implemented in a FPGA.

Certifications

2020 Google Cloud Platform Cloud Architect **GCP**

2020 Google Cloud Platform Data Engineer **GCP**

2014 **ORACLE Administration Workshop** IPN ESIME.

Latest Courses

2020 Azure AZ-900 preparation course Linux Academy. 2020 Google Cloud Architect preparation course

Linux Academy.

2019 Google Cloud Data Engineer preparation course Linux Academy.

2019 Big Data Fundamentals Linux Academy.

Experience

2019-CurrentBig Data Support Engineer.

EPAM Systems

UAM Azc.

Google Cloud Platform.

Providing support to customers using Cloud Platform products, solutions and APIs, including Big Data and related services.

Identify and document product bugs and feature requests and work with internal support teams as well as customers to implement effective solutions.

I work closely with internal support teams to improve cloud products at a senior level.

Working with Big Data technology (Hadoop, MapReduce, HDFS). Writting code using programming languages as Java and Python. Working with NoSQL databases and big data querying tools like Pig, Hive, Impala.

Developing sotutions by using Big Data tools like Apache Beam (Cloud Dataflow) and Apache Airflow (Cloud Composer).

2018-2019 Oracle Developer 4th Source

ESI(Express Scripts).

Working on transformation team, developing PL/SQL code to migrate existing systems to new platforms, in this position, I'm getting lots of experience in Java and tools like Kafka and Attunity.

Developing PL/SQL.

Developing web services using Java EE.

Work with tools like Kafka, Zookeeper, Attunity.

2017-2018 Oracle Senior Developer AsTeci

Banco Azteca.

Member of the team that developed a project called MER, which identified elements that could cause risk on branches, the purpose was to measure risks to take actions and avoid fines.

Devolping PL/SQL code to webapps.

Desing database model to support MER system.

Code functions, procedures, views, sequences, indexes and data

model to interact with Frontend and Backend.